One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Beyond the heavy rain is a rainbow
hageshii ame no mukou kakaru niji wo mita
I'll know the easy answer's a lie
tayasui kotae wa uso dato shiru darou
Vow not to back down to the shouting
dekai koe nanka ni makenai to chikatte
I need you alone to understand tomorrow
anata hitori ni wakatte hoshii ashita
You gave me the time of my life
yume no youna jikan kureta anata
What do I look like? An ANGEL or a DEVIL...
watashi wa dou mieteruno? sorega tenshi ka akuma ka
Beyond the dawn, beyond the dawn
yoake no mukou yoake no mukou
There's so much I want to tell you
hanashitai koto takusan aru nda
Filled with love, with love
ai kometa ai kometa
That can't be written down in a letter
tegami ni kakikirenai omoi da
A small hand in search of eternity
eien wo sagashita chiisana tenohira
"To the Sea Where My Father is!
The Future Bonney Chooses"
Three
Years Ago,
Mt. Corvo,
Goa Kingdom,
East Blue
Gum-Gum...
...Battle Axe!
Did you see that?! Wasn't it awesome?!
Hm? Why are you guys freaking out?
With this power, I can knock anyone down!
Monkey D. Luffy (Age 16)
Even Ace can't beat me!
Dragon...
You seem extremely familiar
with this country.
You even ventured to a small village
on its outskirts
and were watching a particular boy.
Keep talking, if you want to see me killed.
What do you mean?
A child is their parent's weak spot.
I'm sorry.
I'll forget what I saw.
Gum-Gum Battle Axe!
This will be my killer attack!
I'll use it when I face really tough enemies.
When I become a pirate, I'll have a crew.
Then one of my crewmates
could get beaten and captured!
That's when I'll use it!
I'll make them pay!
Whoever the enemy is,
I'll attack with Gum-Gum Battle Axe!
See?!
What?!
Don't worry, I don't eat weaklings!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Who is it?!
What was that presence?
It gave me a chill.
I guess a beast,
like the lord of this mountain,
still lurks here!
Pirates have attacked a merchant ship
and are on the run!
Eliminate the pirate ship!
I'm here to help.
Are you the ones
who were raided by pirates?
They suddenly appeared
and took all the cargo!
How is your ship?
Don't worry!
The fire will be out in no time!
It hurts...
Stay with me! Hang in there!
I'll take him to a hospital
on a nearby island.
Bartholomew Kuma!
What are you doing?!
Eliminate the pirate ship already!
I'm going on ahead. You guys catch up.
Thank you!
Without you, he would have died!
B-Bartholomew Kuma?!
What?!
Surrender yourselves.
Y-Yes, sir!
Guys! Return all the treasure!
Or we're dead men!
"Dear Bonney,
The world is full of more beautiful sights
than any book or picture could describe.
It is brimming with exquisite scenery!
I want to see your face light up
when you see it."
Sorbet Kingdom
Nothing yet?
He's probably busy with his work,
and News Coo may have misplaced it.
But Dad said he'd write me a lot!
You must wait patiently for letters.
I'm sure one'll arrive soon, Bonney.
Oh...
The newspaper and a letter.
- Deliver to the church's mailbox.
- Yes, ma'am!
Is it a letter?!
No, just the newspaper.
Another letter arrived?!
Yes... How many letters is that now?
It's about ten letters a month...
So we've already received dozens.
How does he have so much to write about?
"Dear Bonney"
"Dear Bonney."
What a bunch of crap!
"Lastly, Bonney,
though I've said it countless times,
I love you."
It's your turn, Pert.
What's the matter, Bonney?
Gyogyo.
Let's fight!
Again, Bonney?
What about Jenga?
Fight! Fight! Fight!
You little...
Bonney! Turn back to your original form!
What?
It's time to take your medicine,
Bonney-chan.
What?
Oh, thank you
for taking care of her every day.
Would you like some tea?
Oh... No, thank you.
That's strange.
Was I seeing things?
Bonney looked like a giantess...
Here, Bonney-chan.
It's so bitter! I hate it!
Bear with it. It's good medicine.
It's just a bad-tasting candy.
Grandma Conney, why do Bonney's abilities
have to be kept a secret?
Just to be safe.
A wise wolf hides its fangs.
Marines' Science
Group, Laboratory 8
That's unbelievable, Doctor!
Is it complete already?!
Yeah. Now all I have to do is lift the lab
and my brain into the air with Island Clouds.
Well, half of the stuff you see here
is holograms.
I originally intended to do this
with Punk Hazard.
Nice head-cut.
I feel so light, I could fly.
Kuma!
I heard you're going to
lose your free will.
A human without free will
or a clone with free will...
Who has it worse?
Stop it, Stussy.
You're human.
What does it mean to lose free will?
No matter how much
you claim to follow orders now,
could you, for example, kill a child
if you were told to?
In this research,
the loss of free will means...
...the loss of memories from living as a human
and all human emotions.
All right.
The examination is over. You're all set.
How do you feel?
Are you starting to feel anxious?
No.
I'm more worried about...
You're not being honest.
You'll lose your memories and emotions.
It's impossible to come to terms with it.
Especially, if you have
someone important to you.
But I'll ensure you retain a minimum level of
free will until it's fully complete.
You have roughly a year until then.
A letter again?
As long as I have time,
I want to keep telling Bonney...
...that I love her.
Over the next year, I'm going to write down
a lifetime's worth of feelings.
That's so sweet!
She'll turn nine soon!
I'm sure she has grown a lot.
It hasn't been that long!
"I don't know
when this letter will reach you,
but Bonney, happy ninth birthday.
I'm at Vegapunk's lab now and..."
Bonney!
Happy Birthday!
Grandma Conney's special giant pizza!
Yay! Thanks!
So good!
There's nothing.
No letter has come.
I'm sure one'll arrive soon, Bonney.
Don't you know I'm nine...
Daddy?...
You said you'd write me letters.
Baltigo, Revolutionary
Army Headquarters
Kuma saved us again?
Yes! He helped us out of
a dangerous situation!
Kuma-san!
But he again left without saying a word!
If that's what he wants, don't chase him.
He must have a reason for it.
A reason he can't tell us.
I'm cured!
Look! All the stones are gone!
I'm happy for you, Bonney.
You did so well.
I wanna go outside!
No.
Bonney-chan.
We were told to take care of you
until your tenth birthday.
That's a lie!
You liar!
Vegapunk said I'd be cured in a year!
A year has already passed!
No!
I'm cured now! Leave me alone!
That's too bad...
That woman!
How could she do this to her?
Bonney.
Alpha and her associates
are Government intelligence agents.
What?!
She's not a nurse?!
Apparently,
she was out in town getting drunk
and talking the other day.
She said you were completely cured now.
She said that?!
I don't know what her hidden motive is,
but it's strange to keep you, a healthy person,
locked inside for another six months.
It's also strange
that Kuma hasn't sent a single letter.
Don't you think so?
Yeah...
I've already talked
to Gyogyo and the others.
Make for the port, Bonney.
Go out to sea and meet your father.
I can see him?!
Don't worry.
You'll be able to see him.
Oh?
I'm returning to the palace.
Fine. Take care.
Gyogyo's group,
they're not ordinary fishermen.
They're legendary ruffian fishermen...
...who strike fear into pirates and beasts alike!
They'll surely help you see your father!
I'm outside!
Dirt...
Wind...
Grass...
The sky...
The sun!
Bonney is actually walking outside...
It's a miracle! There really is a God!
Let's set sail!
Bonney! This way!
Gyogyo! Totts! Potato!
Look! I'm outside!
Where is Bonney?!
Queen Dowager Conney!
But you just went out...
What's going on?!
I'm Bonney!
You liar!
Look at that!
I made the ship look like pizza!
I love it!
How dare she fool me.
This is unforgivable!
All right! Let's go!
Hold it right there!
It's Alpha!
Quick! Accelerate!
If the subject of surveillance escapes, I'm
permitted to use any means short of murder...
...to subdue her!
That'll make it so much easier!
She came flying!
She uses the Six Powers,
the Government's combat techniques!
If I get caught here,
I'll be...
For those aiding her however,
no holds are barred!
No...
I don't want that!
Dad...
What should I do?
Dad, what does Nika look like?
No one knows, but...
Nika!
Distorted Future!
You can transform! I knew it was you!
Bonney?!
They say his body
had properties like rubber,
and he fought however he fancied.
You shitty brat!
Nika-Like Future!
What?!
The escape of Bonney, the hostage, was
reported to the World Government at once.
And the fishing boat in search of her father...
...would eventually evolve into an infamous
new-era pirate ship, much like Luffy's.
I can't protect anyone again
mata daremo mamorenai no
It's my fault that the voice is fading away
kiekakaru koe wa boku no sei
I don't even have time to look down
utsumuku hima mo nai no
Gravel marks on my palms
tenohira ni tsuku jari no ato
Start moving again, my ship
mata ugokidase boku no fune yo
Though I can't fly in the broad sky
hiroi sora wa tobenai kedo
I can light up the deep sea
fukai umi wa teraseru kara
We
bokura wa
EVERYDAY, can't let this be the end
EVERYDAY owarenai
EVERYDAY, can't be defeated
EVERYDAY makerenai
We have something here to protect
mamoru mono ga koko niwa aru
This may not be what I expected
yosou chigai kamo?
But we can't stop now
tomarenai yo mou
We go on, sharing loneliness
kodoku wo ima wakeai susumu
Don't be afraid
ojikedukuna yo
I'm not the same person I was that day
ano hi no boku to chigau kara
No one can stand in my way
dare nimo jama dekinai yo
Now, move aside
saa doite
Conquer the world, believe in the future
sekai wo seishite mirai wo shinjite
Count up the nights
ikutsu mono yoru kazoete
What did you see? What did you learn?
nani wo mite nani wo shitte
To realize what was important
taisetsu na koto ni kiduita no